There is... a house... in New Orleans
They call the Rising Sun
And it's been the ruin of many a poor boy
And God, I know I'm one.
[Instrumental]
My mother was a tailor!
She sewed my new blue jeans!
My father was a gamblin' man!
Down in New Orleans
Now the only thing a gambler needs,
Is a suitcase and trunk!
And the only time he'll be satisfied
Is when he's on a drunk
[Instrumental]
Oh mother...
Tell your children,
Not to do what I have done!
Spend your lives in sin and misery!
In the House of the Rising Sun
[Instrumental]
Well, I got one foot on the platform!
The other foot on the train!
I'm goin' back to New Orleans,
To wear that ball and chain!
[Instrumental]
Well, there is a house in New Orleans!
They call the Rising Sun!
And it's been the ruin of many a poor boy!
And God I know I'm one
[Instrumental]