I don't like you T-series
Nothing personal, kid
But I must go all out
Just this once
Bobs or Vegana which ever will it be?
Sit the fuck down T-Series
I'm here to spill the real tea
You tryna dethrone me from the spot of number one
But, "You India, you lose"
So, best think you haven't won
When I'm through with you, we're gonna be completely fuckin' done
'cuz we only just begun
I review you ðŸ‘ ðŸ‘ zero, bye, bitch gone
So, come on, T-series, looking hungry for some drama?
Here, let me serve you Bitch Lasagna.
Bitch Lasagna
T-Series ain't nothing but a Bitch, Lasagna
Look at T-Series they just cryin' for their mamma
Bitch Lasagna
T-Series ain't nothing but a
T-Series just wet themselves in their pajamas
So, who the hell is Bob, and why you wanna kiss him?
(Ew)
I'm a Blue-Eyes White Dragon while you're just Dark Magician (oof)
You got a fifth of the population in your nation but
I got nine year olds
Of worlds so hold your defecation
(OOPS)
Motu Patlu, What the fuck is that
Is that even supposed to mean?
Your language sounds like it
Came from a mumble rap community
No Papa, No Papa
Yes Papa
Johnny
Now down all of this sugar
and let's throw this fucking party with some-
Bitch Lasagna
Look at T-Series they just cryin' for their mamma
T-Series ain't nothing but a
Bitch, Lasagna
Bitch Lasagna
Look at T-Series just wet themselves in their pajamas
T-Series ain't nothing but a
Bitch Lasagna
You got a population of 1.32 Billion but
Most of your videos can't seem to hit even a million.
SUB BOT